const SocialReforms = [
	{
		questionText: 'Adhi Bhramma Samaj formed in?',
		ans: ['1878'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Ved samaj in?',
		ans: ['1864'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Bhramma samaj of India',
		ans: ['1866'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Tatva bhodini Samaj',
		ans: ['Debendranath'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Atmiya Sabha',
		ans: ['RRM'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Bhang sabha Prakasika',
		ans: ['RRM'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Arya Samaj',
		ans: ['Dayanad saraswathi,1975'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'who started suddhi movement',
		ans: ['Dayanad saraswathi'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dayanadh Anglo vedic college ',
		ans: ['Hans Raj @ Lahore'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Ramakrishna Mission in?',
		ans: ['1897'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Parthana samaj in?',
		ans: ['Atmaram & panduranga, in 1867'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The servents of Indian society',
		ans: ['Gopal krishna Ghokle'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'East India Assosiation',
		ans: ['Dadabai Navroji'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Bombay president assosiation',
		ans: ['Baduruudin Tayyab'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Satyabhodak Samaj',
		ans: ['Jyothibhai Phule'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Father of Bengali pharse',
		ans: ['Eswar chandra vidya sagar'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Arya Mahila samaj',
		ans: ['Pandit Ramabai'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Rehnumai Mazdyasan sabha',
		ans: ['Dadabhai navroji', 'parsi reform'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'All India kisan Sabha',
		ans: ['Swami sahajanand saraswathi'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Bombay Mills Assosiation',
		ans: ['Narayan Lokahand-father of Indian workers moments'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Indian Assosiation',
		ans: ['Subendranath Benerjee & Anand mohan Bose'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Asiatic society',
		ans: ['William Jhons, in 1784'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Vahabi Movement',
		ans: ['Syed Ahmed Barveli'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Aligard movement',
		ans: ['Syed Ahmed Khan'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Ahamadiya Movement',
		ans: ['Mirja Ahamed'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Devbandh Movement',
		ans: ['Kasim navnatvi & Rashid Ahmed Gangoi'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Kilafat Andholan',
		ans: ['Mohammed Ali & Shaukat Ali'],
	},

];

export default SocialReforms;
